Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part II WAG.025.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Foreign Countries
  - Belgium, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Belgium, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 32)
    Microfilm reel#: 238
  - Belgium, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Belgium, 1955-1956 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Bolivia, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Bolivia, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Brazil, 1948-1953 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Brazil, 1954-1956 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Bulgaria, 1948-1952 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Canada: General, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Canada: General, 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Canada: General, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Canada: General, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Canada: General, 1953-1954 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Canada: General, 1955-1956 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1948 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Canada: Montreal, Feb 1948 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Montreal, Mar 1948 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Canada: Montreal, Apr 1948 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    Microfilm reel#: 239
  - Canada: Montreal, May 1948 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1948-Jul 1948 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Canada: Montreal, Aug 1948 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Canada: Montreal, Sep 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Canada: Montreal, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1949-Feb 1949 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Canada: Montreal, Mar 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Canada: Montreal, May 1949-Jun 1949 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jul 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Canada: Montreal, Sep 1949-Oct 1949 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Canada: Montreal, Nov 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1950-Feb 1950 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Canada: Montreal, Mar 1950-Apr 1950 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    Microfilm reel#: 240
  - Canada: Montreal, May 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jul 1950-Aug 1950 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Canada: Montreal, Sep 1950-Oct 1950 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Canada: Montreal, Nov 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Canada: Montreal, Apr 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jul 1951-Sep 1951 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Canada: Montreal, Oct 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1952-May 1952 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1953-May 1953 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    Microfilm reel#: 241
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1954-May 1954 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jan 1955-May 1955 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Canada: Montreal, Jun 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Canada: Montreal, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Canada: Ottawa, 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Canada: Toronto, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1950 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    Microfilm reel#: 242
  - Canada: Toronto, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Canada: Toronto, 1955-1956 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Canada: Vancouver, 1953-1956 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Canada: Winnipeg, 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Chile, 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - China, 1948 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - China, 1949 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - China, 1950-1955 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Colombia, 1948-1955 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Costa Rica, 1950-1954 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Cuba, 1948-1953 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Curacao, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Cyprus, 1948 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Denmark, 1948-1956 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Egypt, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - England, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    Microfilm reel#: 243
  - England, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - England, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - England, 1951-1952 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - England, 1953-1956 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - France, Jan 1948 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - France, Feb 1948 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - France, Mar 1948 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - France, Apr 1948 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - France, May 1948 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    Microfilm reel#: 244
  - France, Jun 1948 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - France, Jul 1948 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - France, Aug 1948 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - France, Sep 1948 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - France, Oct 1948 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - France, Nov 1948 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - France, Dec 1, 1948Dec 25, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    Microfilm reel#: 245
  - France, Dec 26, 1948Dec 31, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - France, Jan 1949 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - France, Feb 1949 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - France, Mar 1949 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - France, Apr 1949 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    Microfilm reel#: 246
  - France, May 1949 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - France, Jun 1949 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - France, Jul 1949 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - France, Aug 1949 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - France, Sep 1949 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    Microfilm reel#: 247
  - France, Oct 1949 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - France, Nov 1949 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - France, Dec 1949 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - France: Roumanian Refugees, 1948-1950 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - France, Jan 1950 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - France, Feb 1950 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - France, Mar 1950 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    Microfilm reel#: 248
  - France, Apr 1950 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - France, May 1950 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - France, Jun 1950 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - France, Jul 1950 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - France, Aug 1950 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - France, Sep 1950 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - France, Oct 1950 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - France, Nov 1950 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - France, Dec 1950 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - France, Jan 1951 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - France, Feb 1951 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    Microfilm reel#: 249
  - France, Mar 1951 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - France, Apr 1951 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - France, May 1951 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - France, Jun 1951 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - France, Jul 1951 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - France, Aug 1951 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - France, Sep 1951 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - France, Oct 1951 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - France, Nov 1951 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - France, Dec 1951 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - France, Jan 1952 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - France, Feb 1952 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    Microfilm reel#: 250
  - France, Mar 1952 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - France, Apr 1952 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - France, May 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - France, Jul 1952-Aug 1952 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - France, Sep 1952 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - France, Oct 1952 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - France, Nov 1952 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - France, Dec 1952 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - France, Jan 1953-Feb 1953 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - France, Mar 1953-Apr 1953 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    Microfilm reel#: 251
  - France, May 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - France, Jul 1953-Aug 1953 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - France, Sep 1953-Oct 1953 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - France, Nov 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - France, Jan 1954-Feb 1954 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - France, Mar 1954-Apr 1954 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    Microfilm reel#: 252
  - France, May 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - France, Jul 1954-Aug 1954 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - France, Sep 1954-Oct 1954 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - France, Nov 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - France, Jan 1955-Mar 1955 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - France, Apr 1955-Jun 1955 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - France, Jul 1955-Sep 1955 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - France, Oct 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    Microfilm reel#: 253
  - France, Jan 1955-Mar 1955 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - France, Apr 1955-Jun 1955 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - France, Jul 1955-Sep 1955 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - France, Oct 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Germany, Jan 1948 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Germany, Feb 1948 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    Microfilm reel#: 254
  - Germany, Mar 1948 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Germany, Apr 1948 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Germany, May 1948 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Germany, Jun 1948-Jul 1948 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    Microfilm reel#: 255
  - Germany, Aug 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Germany, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Germany: Lists, 1948 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Germany: Int'l Rescue & Relief Comm., 1948-1949 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Germany, Jan 1949-Mar 1949 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Germany, Apr 1949-Jul 1949 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    Microfilm reel#: 256
  - Germany, Jul 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Germany, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Germany: Lists of Bundists, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Germany, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Germany, Jan 1951-Apr 1951 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Germany, May 1951-Aug 1951 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Germany, Sep 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Germany, Jan 1952-Mar 1952 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Germany, Apr 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    Microfilm reel#: 257
  - Germany, Jul 1952-Sep 1952 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Germany, Oct 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Germany (incl. lists of TB cases), 1952 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Germany, Jan 1953-Mar 1953 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Germany, Apr 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Germany, Jul 1953-Nov 1953 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Germany, Dec 1953 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Germany, Jan 1954-Mar 1954 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Germany, Apr 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Germany, Jul 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 87, Folder 25)
    Microfilm reel#: 258
  - Germany, Oct 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Germany, 1955-1956 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jan 1948 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Feb 1948 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Mar 1948-Apr 1948 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, May 1948 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jun 1948 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jul 1948 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    Microfilm reel#: 259
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Aug 1948 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Sep 1948 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Oct 1948 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Nov 1948 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Dec 1948 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jan 1949 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Feb 1949 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Mar 1949 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    Microfilm reel#: 260
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Apr 1949 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, May 1949 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jun 1949 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Jul 1949 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Aug 1949 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Sep 1949 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Oct 1949 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    Microfilm reel#: 261
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Nov 1949 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Dec 1949 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, 1950 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, Lists, 1949-1950 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Germany: Bella Meiksin, 1951 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Jan 1948-Mar 1948 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Apr 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Jul 1948-Aug 1948 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Sep 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    Microfilm reel#: 262
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Jan 1948-May 1948 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Germany: N. Gierowitz, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Greece, 1948-1949 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Hungary, 1947-1949 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Hungary, 1951-1956 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - India, 1950 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Israel (Palestine), 1948 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Israel, Jan 1949-Mar 1949 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Israel, Apr 1949-Jun 1949 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Israel, Jul 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    Microfilm reel#: 263
  - Israel, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Israel, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Israel, Jul 1950-Oct 1950 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Israel, Nov 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Israel, Jan 1951-Feb 1951 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Israel, Mar 1951-Apr 1951 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Israel, May 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    Microfilm reel#: 264
  - Israel, Jul 1951-Sep 1951 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Israel, Oct 1951-Nov 1951 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Israel, Dec 1951 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Israel, Jan 1952 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Israel, Feb 1952 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Israel, Mar 1952 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    Microfilm reel#: 265
  - Israel, Apr 1952 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Israel, May 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Israel, Jul 1952-Aug 1952 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Israel, Sep 1952-Nov 1952 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Israel, Dec 1952 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Israel, Jan 1953-Mar 1953 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    Microfilm reel#: 266
  - Israel, Apr 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Israel, Jul 1953-Sep 1953 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Israel, Oct 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Israel, Jan 1954-Mar 1954 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Israel, Apr 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Microfilm reel#: 267
  - Israel, Jul 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Israel, Oct 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Israel, Jan 1955-Mar 1955 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Israel, Apr 1955-Jun 1955 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Israel, Jul 1955-Aug 1955 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    Microfilm reel#: 268
  - Israel, Sep 1955-Oct 1955 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Israel, Nov 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Israel, Jan 1956 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Israel, Feb 1956 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Israel, Mar 1956-Apr 1956 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Israel, May 1956-Jun 1956 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Israel, Jul 1956-Sep 1956 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Israel, Oct 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    Microfilm reel#: 269
  - Italy, Jan 1948-Feb 1948 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Italy, Mar 1948-Apr 1948 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Italy, May 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Italy, Jul 1948-Aug 1948 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Italy, Sep 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    Microfilm reel#: 270
  - Italy, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Italy, Jan 1949-Mar 1949 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Italy, Apr 1949-Jun 1949 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Italy, Jul 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Italy, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Italy, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Italy, Jul 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Italy, 1951 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Italy, 1952 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Italy, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Italy, 1954-1956 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Japan, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Latin America: General, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Mexico, Jan 1948-Mar 1948 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    Microfilm reel#: 271
  - Mexico, Apr 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Mexico, Jul 1948-Sep 1948 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Mexico, Oct 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Mexico, 1949 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Mexico, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Mexico, Jul 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Mexico, Jan 1951-Aug 1951 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Mexico, Sep 1951-Oct 1951 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Mexico, Nov 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Mexico, Jan 1952-Aug 1952 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Mexico, Sep 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Mexico, Jan 1953-Sep 1953 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    Microfilm reel#: 272
  - Mexico, Oct 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Mexico, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Mexico, 1955 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Mexico, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Morocco, 1948-1955 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Netherlands, 1948-1950 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Norway, 1948-1949 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Norway, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Norway, 1952-1955 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Norway, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Panama, 1951-1952 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Philippines, 1949-1950 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Poland, [1946-1947], Jan 1948 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Poland, Feb 1948 (Box 92, Folder 36)
    Microfilm reel#: 273
  - Poland, Mar 1948 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Poland, Apr 1948 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Poland, May 1948 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Poland, Jun 1948 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Poland, Jul 1949 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Poland, Aug 1948 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Poland, Sep 1948 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Poland, Oct 1948 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Poland, Nov 1948 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Poland, Dec 1948 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Poland, Jan 1949-Jun 1949 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Poland, Jul 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Poland, 1950-1953 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Poland, 1954-1955 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    Microfilm reel#: 274
  - Poland, 1956 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Portugal, 1950 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Roumania, Jan 1948-Jul 1948 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Roumania, Aug 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Roumania, Jan 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Roumania, Sep 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Roumania, Jan 1950-Mar 1950 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Roumania, Apr 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    Microfilm reel#: 275
  - Roumania, 1951-1956 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - South Africa, 1948-1956 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Union, 1948-1956 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Spain, 1948-1954 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Surinam, 1948 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Sweden, Jan 1948 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Sweden, Feb 1948 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Sweden, Mar 1948 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - Sweden, Apr 1948 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Sweden, May 1948 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Sweden, Jun 1948 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Microfilm reel#: 276
  - Sweden, Jul 1948 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, Aug 1948 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, Sep 1948 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, Oct 1948 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Sweden, Nov 1948 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    Microfilm reel#: 277
  - Sweden, 1948-12-01-1948-12-20 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, 1948-12-21-1948-12-31 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, Jan 1949 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    Microfilm reel#: 278
  - Sweden, Feb 1949 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Sweden, Mar 1949 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Sweden, Apr 1949 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Sweden, May 1949 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    Microfilm reel#: 279
  - Sweden, Jun 1949 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Sweden, Jul 1949 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Sweden, Aug 1949 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Sweden, Sep 1949 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Sweden, Oct 1949 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    Microfilm reel#: 280
  - Sweden, Nov 1949 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Sweden, Dec 1949-Jan 1949 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Sweden, Dec 1949-Jan 1949 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, 1949-01-1951-06 (Box 573)
  - Sweden, Jan 1950-Feb 1950 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, Mar 1950-Apr 1950 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, May 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, Jul 1950-Aug 1950 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    Microfilm reel#: 281
  - Sweden, Sep 1950-Oct 1950 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Sweden, Nov 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Sweden, Jan 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, Jul 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    Microfilm reel#: 282
  - Sweden, Jan 1952-May 1952 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Sweden, Jun 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Sweden, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Sweden, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Sweden, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Sweden, 1956 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Switzerland, 1948 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    Microfilm reel#: 283
  - Sweden, 1949 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Sweden, 1950 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Sweden, 1951-1952 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Sweden, 1953-1956 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - Trinidad, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Uruguay, 1948-1950 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Uruguay, 1951-1956 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Venezuela, 1948-1954 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Yugoslavia, 1948-1954 (Box 94, Folder 28)
- Series IV: Immigration, Resettlement and Refugee Aid
  - Subseries IV:A: General Files
    Scope and Contents note
    - arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - 1. Topical
      - Affidavits and Forms, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 1)
        Microfilm reel#: 284
      - Agudath Israel of America, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Aid: General, undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Aid: General, [Dec 1947], 1948-1951 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Aid: General, 1952-1956 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Aid: Argentina, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Aid: Books, 1952-1955 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Aid: Bulgaria, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Aid: China, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Aid: Cyprus, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Aid: Czechoslovakia, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Aid: England, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Aid: France, 1949-1953 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Aid: Housing, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Aid: Hungary, undated (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Aid: Israel, 1949-1956 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Aid: Medical, 1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - Aid: Poland, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Aid: Roumanians, 1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Aid: Spain, 1948-1956 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Aid: Sweden, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 21)
      - Aid: USSR, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - Alperin, Rose, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - American Committee of O.S.E., 1948 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      - American Far Eastern Society, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 27)
        Microfilm reel#: 285
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee, 1951-1956 (Box 95, Folder 28)
      - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee: Machines, 1948-1950 (Box 95, Folder 29)
      - American Red Cross, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 30)
      - "Americanizing Our Immigration Laws", 1948 (Box 95, Folder 31)
      - Anti-Defamation League, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 32)
      - Arrivals (Name, Ship, Dates), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 33)
      - Australia: Applicants for Visas (A to M) (Box 95, Folder 34)
      - Australia: Applicants for Visas (N to Z), 1948 (Box 95, Folder 35)
      - Birman, M., 1949-1955 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      - Blatman, Shmulik: Fund, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 37)
      - Blatman, Shmulik: Fund, Jan 1955 (Box 95, Folder 38)
      - Blatman, Shmulik: Fund, Feb 1955-Dec 1956 (Box 95, Folder 39)
      - Blind Fund (Israel), 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 40)
      - Bomze and Rubinstein (Poets), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 41)
      - Botwinik, David, 1953-1956 (Box 95, Folder 42)
        Microfilm reel#: 286
      - Brumberg, Joseph, 1948 (Box 95, Folder 43)
      - Canada, 1948-1955 (Box 95, Folder 44)
      - Canada: Garment Workers and Furriers, 1948-1949 (Box 95, Folder 45)
      - Care, Inc., 1948, 1952-1954 (Box 95, Folder 46)
      - Care, Inc., 1955 (Box 95, Folder 47)
      - Care, Inc., 1956 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Central Committee of Jews in Poland, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Chanin, Nathan, 1948-1949 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Chattanooga, TN, 1950-1954 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Chaver Hilf, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Chaver Hilf, Jan 1951-Apr 1951 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Chaver Hilf, May 1951-Aug 1951 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Chaver Hilf, Sep 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Chaver Hilf, Jan 1952-Feb 1952 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Chaver Hilf (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Chaver Hilf, Apr 1952-Sep 1952 (Box 96, Folder 11)
        Microfilm reel#: 287
      - Chaver Hilf, Oct 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Chaver Hilf, Jan 1953-Jul 1953 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Chaver Hilf, Aug 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - Chaver Hilf, Jan 1954-Feb 1954 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Chaver Hilf, Mar 1954-Apr 1954 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Chaver Hilf, May 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Chaver Hilf: Letters from Israel, Jan 1951-May 1951 (Box 96, Folder 18)